Guide to the Joseph Verner Reed (1937-) papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Joseph Verner Reed (1937-2016) papers
1939-2014
MS 1964
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
38.75
(46 boxes)
The Joseph Verner Reed (1937-) papers consist of correspondence, scrapbooks, speeches, topical files and photographs. The papers primarily document Reed's service as ambassador to Morocco (1981-1985) and his tenure as special assistant to David Rockefeller at Chase Manhattan Bank, which includes materials documenting Rockefeller's role in gaining permission for the exiled Shah of Iran to undergo medical treatment in the United States in 1980.
Reed, Joseph Verner, 1937-2016
Arrangement
Arranged in four series and one addition: I. General Files, 1939-1999. II. Speeches, 1981-2009. III. Topical Files, 1947-2011. IV. Photographs, 1969-2007.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Joseph Verner Reed, 2011, 2015.
Conditions Governing Access
Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
Scope and Contents
The Joseph Verner Reed (1937-) papers consist of correspondence, scrapbooks, speeches, topical files and photographs. The papers are arranged in four series: General Files, Speeches, Topical Files, and Photographs. The first series, General Files, contain personal and professional papers of Joseph Verner Reed from 1939 to 1999. The second series, Speeches, consist of Reed's speeches from 1981 to 2009 with an index listing the topic of the speech, location of the speech and the date the speech was given. The third series, Topical Files, contain records of Reed's tenure as the U.S. Ambassador to Morocco, service awards Reed received from over twenty-eight countries, files related to the exile of the Shah of Iran, and newspaper clippings and chronological files of Reed's work with the United Nations. The fourth series, Photographs, contain images of events attended by Reed from 1969-2007.
Biographical / Historical
Joseph Verner Reed (Jr.) was born in New York City on December 17, 1937. He was a graduate of Deerfield Academy and received his Bachelor of Arts from Yale University, Class of 1961.
Following his university studies, he joined the World Bank as private secretary to President Eugene Robert Black where he served from 1961 to 1963. From 1963 to 1981, he was vice president and assistant to the Chairman of the Chase Manhattan Bank, David Rockefeller.
Reed was appointed by President Ronald Reagan as Ambassador of the United States of America to the Kingdom of Morocco in 1981 and in 1985 as the Representative of the United States to the Economic and Social Council of the United Nations as Deputy Permanent Representative at the United States Mission. In 1987, he was appointed Under-Secretary-General of the United Nations for Politicial and General Assembly Affairs. In early 1989, President George H.W. Bush appointed Reed the Chief of Protocol at the White House, where he served until late 1991.
In 1992, the then Secretary-General of the United Nations, Dr. Boutros Boutros-Ghali, appointed Reed Under-Secretary-General of the United Nations and Special Representative for Public Affairs, concluding his assignment in February 1997. In June 1997, Secretary-General of the United Nations, Kofi A. Annan, appointed Reed as President of the Staff Management Coordination Committee (SMCC), the highest internal body of the World Organization. Ambassador Reed served as SMCC president for seven years, concluding his assignment in December 2004. Reed died on September 29, 2016 in Greenwich, Connecticut.
Ambassadors -- Morocco; Diplomacy; Morocco -- Foreign relations -- United States; United States -- Foreign relations -- Morocco; Mohammad Reza Pahlavi, Shah of Iran, 1919-1980; Reed, Joseph Verner, 1937-2016; Rockefeller, David, 1915-2017; Chase Manhattan Bank; United Nations
- General Files, 1939-1999; Series I
  Arrangement
  Material is arranged alphabetically by topic, personal name, and title.
  - Autographs and letters, 1939-1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Chase Group
    - Correspondence: David Rockefeller, 1980 December-1981 June (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Washington appointments
      - December 2-5, 1980, 1980 October-December (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - December 11, 1980, 1980 September-December (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Letters concerning "Crotchets", 1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Reed, Joseph V.
    - Articles and photograph, 1970-1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - "Farewell to a King", 1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Jottings file, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Notes, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Passports, 1940s-1960s (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Personal correspondence and articles, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Twenty-fifth anniversary: drafts of letter, notes, and clippings, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Utah State University commencement memorabilia for honorary degree, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Writings and newspaper clippings, 1953-1999, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Speeches, 1981-2009; Series II
  General
  The speech files include correspondence and newspaper clippings.
  - Index to speeches, 1981-1985, 1992-1995, 2000-2009 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Speeches
    - 1981-1984 (Box 3, Folder 2-8)
    - 1985-1988 (Box 4, Folder 1-7)
    - 1988-1991 (Box 5, Folder 1-5)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 1-4)
    - 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 1-5)
    - 1997-2005 (Box 8, Folder 1-5)
    - 2005-2009, undated (Box 9, Folder 1-3)
- Topical, 1947-2011; Series III
  - Ambassador to Morocco
    - General files
      Materials are listed alphabetically by topic, personal name, and title.
      - Afghanistan, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Briefing memoranda and ephemera, 1981 July-October (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Butcher, Willard C., letter regarding appointment of Reed as Moroccan ambassador, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Confirmation hearings
        The majority of these hearings were held in 1989, but are filed here as they reference events which ocurred while Reed was ambassador.
        - Senator Helms's first set of questions, April 7, 1989, 1989 April-May (Box 10, Folder 4)
        - Senator Helms's second set of questions to Secretary Baker dated May 11, 1989, 1989 May-June (Box 10, Folder 5)
        - Thank you letters to various committee members and others, 1989 April-July (Box 10, Folder 6)
        - Miscellaneous notes, 1989 April-September (Box 10, Folder 7)
        - Notes and briefings on nomination, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Famous signatures, 1962-1968 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Farewell "Torch" letter, 1985 April-May (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - "From the Ambassador" notes and remarks, 1985 January-May (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Internal Chase country updates, 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Interview and resignation letter, 1987-1991 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - "Is Morocco Important?", 1985 March (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - JVR profile, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - Libya, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 16)
      - Moroccan-American Foundation
        - Aspen Institute Conference, Feb. 25-March 1, 1985
          - 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 1)
          - Past - Present - Future, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 2)
        - New officers and board of directors, 1985 March (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Morocco Embassy: inspection report, draft, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Press releases, newspaper clippings, and correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Resignation: correspondence and memoranda, 1981-1985 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Ronald Reagan letter to Reed, 1981 September 30 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Safari to Morocco in January 1982, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Staffing budget and briefing paper, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Swearing-in ceremony, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Thursday-events of the day, 1981 October 29 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Visit of Jeane J. Kirkpatrick to Morocco: remarks and itinerary, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Voice of America
        - 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 5)
        - 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - "Welcome Kit": Ambassador to distinquished visitors, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence
      - General, 1981-1985 (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
        Includes newspaper clippings.
      - "Ambassadorgrams": brief messages to embassy staff, 1981-1985 (Box 13, Folder 3-4)
      - Thank-you letters, 1981-1985 (Box 13, Folder 5-6)
        Letters are arranged chronologically.
      - "Very Important" letters, 1983-1985 (Box 13, Folder 7-8)
    - Public pronouncements, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 1-3)
    - Scrapbooks of photographs and newspaper clippings
      - 1981 September 5-1982 February 11 (Box 15)
      - 1982 February 12-June 30 (Box 16)
      - 1982 July 12-1983 April 13 (Box 17)
      - 1983 April 14-August 11 (Box 18)
      - 1983 August 11-October 19 (Box 19)
      - 1983 November 2-1984 April 20 (Box 20)
      - 1984 April 20-October 30 (Box 21)
      - 1984 October 31-1985 May 26 (Box 22)
  - Decoration ceremonies
    Materials are arranged alphabetically by country.
    - Argentina, 1989-1993 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Austria, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Bolivia, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Brazil, 1991-1992 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Chad, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Chile, 1988-1994 (Box 23, Folder 6-7)
    - Columbia, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - The Congo, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Costa Rica, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Cote d'Ivoire (Ivory Coast), 1991-1994 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Denmark, 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Ecuador, 1986-1990 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Egypt, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - El Salvador, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - France, 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Holy See (Vatican), 1989-1994 (Box 24, Folder 6-8)
    - Italy, 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Korea, 1990-1992 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Mali, 1989-1991 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Mexico, 1991-1993 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Niger, 1987, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Paraguay, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Peru, 1991-1992 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Senegal, 1988-1993 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Spain, 1991-1992 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Togo, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - United States
      - American Society of the Order of St. John of Jerusalem, 1989-1992 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Secretary of State certificate, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Venezuela, 1990-1991 (Box 26, Folder 5-7)
  - Shah of Iran
    Materials are arranged alphabetically by topic, personal name, and title.
    - ABC News: "America Held Hostage:The Secret Negotiations" transcript, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Archives -- record summary (Chase), 1980 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Armao breakfast, notes, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - "Big Four" -- notes and telegrams, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Bohlen, Baron von Krupp von -- correspondence and memorabilia, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Cairo trip
      - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Notes, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Chancellor's luncheon and meeting-notes and correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Children's education
      - Research, notes, and correspondence, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence and ephemera, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Communications to the Empress of Iran: notes and correspondence, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Congressional investigation
      - Blocked assets-testimony transcripts and research, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Hansen report, correspondence and articles, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Questions and answers, Undated (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Contingency plan -- Shah of Iran's death, itinerary, notes, and remarks, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence and notes, 1980-1981 (Box 27, Folder 16-17)
    - Counsel -- Iranian government: memoranda, research materials, and transcripts, 1975-1980 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - "The Eagle has Landed"-meeting transcript, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Executive order
      - McCloy, John J.-correspondence and memoranda, 1979-1980 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Reed, Joseph Verner-correspondence, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Giles, Frank -- Florida: correspondence and telegrams, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Huyser, Robert E., General
      - Correspondence, memoranda, and articles, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Dinner at Knickerbocker Club: meeting transcripts, notes, and photographs, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Scott Air Force Base-report and correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Immigration-memoranda, reports, and correspondence, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Interview with Robert Armao-meeting notes, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Interviews "EFS" [Eugene F. Swanzey?]: notes, Circa 1980 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - "Iran Papers" article, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Iran Past Dues -- financial statements, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Kean, B. H., Dr., lawsuit: correspondence and legal documents, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Kissinger, Henry
      - Article: Shah of Iran, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 15)
      - Edited remarks at IAC, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Lawsuit against Iran-notes and news clippings, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Lenczowski, George, Professor
      - "The Black Book"
        - Correspondence and memoranda, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 1)
        - Review correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Consulting agreement with David Rockefeller, 1979-1980 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence and research documents for consultation project with David Rockefeller, 1980-1981 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - New York visit: correspondence and travel notes, 1979-1980 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - Notes, correspondence, and expense reports, 1979-1980 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - Research materials and Emilio Francolini correspondence and memorabilia, 1979-1980 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Revolution in Iran: A Historical Documentation second edition and correspondence, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Writings and publications, 1979-1980 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Luncheon January 27, 1981 regarding Executive Order and blocking of H.I.M.'s assets (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Mexican promise, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Milbank-correspondence and memoranda, 1979-1980 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1976-1979 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Nahavandi, H., 1980-1981 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Newsom, David, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Payment snafu, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Photographs, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Princess Ashraf and Chase Bank re: Iran, correspondence, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Real estate, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Recycling petrodollars, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Reed, Joseph V. and David Rockefeller statements, 1979, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Relocation Project
      - Reed, Joseph V. and David Rockefeller schedules, 1979-1980 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Rockefeller, David, statement and ephemera, 1979-1981 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Shah of Iran-letters, articles, and statements, 1947-1980 (Box 31, Folder 6-7)
    - Review Project -- Howard D. Monroe (HDM), 1980 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - River Club
      - Breakfast, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Dinner, August 19, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Roosevelt, A. B., Jr., reports, 1979-1980 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Roosevelt, David
      - Correspondence regarding Shah of Iran
        - Comments against his U.S. relocation, 1979-1980 (Box 31, Folder 12-13)
        - Comments in favor of relocation to U.S., 1979-1980 (Box 31, Folder 14-15)
        - Customers close Chase bank accounts, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 1)
        - General opinions, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 2)
        - Newspaper clippings sent to DR, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Edited drafts of memoirs: Chapters 16, 24, and 25 regarding Shah of Iran, 1997-1999 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Interview questions, Undated (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Interview regarding Shah of Iran, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - "Late Shah of Iran"-draft essay and correspondence, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Memorandum on Chase Group and Shah of Iran, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Schedule additions, 1977-1979 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Shah meetings lists, 1980-1981 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Statements, correspondence and memoranda, 1979-1982 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Statements regarding Shah, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Trip to Middle East, 1974 January 18-February 3 (Box 32, Folder 13)
        Typescript of notes taken by Richard G. Rockefeller.
    - Rockefeller family correspondence, 1957-1980 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Schackne, Robert, CBS Evening News, 1981 February 17 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Shah of Iran
      - Book review, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - Death, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 17-18)
      - Exile, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 19)
      - Exile chronology, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Shapiro, Harvey, project, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Smith, Terence, interview, Circa 1981 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Special crash project, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Stationery, Undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Sullivan, William H.
      - Foreign policy article, 1980 fall (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Luncheon with Shah of Iran, 1981 March 17 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - United Nations
      - Newspaper clippings, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Security Council on Iran, 1979 December (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - U.S.S. Pueblo research articles, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Wall Street Journal exchange, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Washington Post -- Pahlavi Family, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Work session notes
      - 1980 May 6 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - 1980 May 7 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Yazdi, Ibrahim, Minister of Foreign Affairs, Iran: meeting with Council on Foreign Relations, Inc.
      - Correspondence and transcript of meeting, 1979 October 2-30 (Box 33, Folder 14)
      - Recording of meeting, 1979 October 2; 1 (Box 34)
        Conditions Governing Access
        Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
  - United Nations files
    See also: Confirmation hearings, box 10, folders 4-7.
    - General chronological files
      - 1991-1996 (Box 35, Folder 1-6)
      - 2008-2011 (Box 36, Folder 1-3)
    - Correspondence
      - Appointment and resignation as Under Secretarty General, 1987-1989 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Denial of visa for Yasser Arafat, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Newspaper clippings and public statements
      - Books I-VII, 1980-1988 (Box 37, Folder 1-8)
      - Books VIII-XII, 1988-1991 (Box 38, Folder 1-7)
      - 1985-1987 (Box 39, Folder 1-4)
- Photographs, 1969-2007; Series IV
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of photographic images and one sketch. Materials are arranged in three boxes by size and chronologically within each box.
  - David Rockefeller, autographed, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Joseph Verner Reed and President Richard M. Nixon in Morocco, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - "Fete du Trône," Casablanca, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Joseph Verner Reed and Vice President George Bush, autographed, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Richard Casey, autographed, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Joseph Verner Reed swearing-in ceremony, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Joseph Verner Reed and President George Bush, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Business Council for the United Nations (BCUN) Dinner -- Joseph Verner Reed, Mrs. Susan Baker, and Margaret Thatcher, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Joseph Verner Reed miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Joseph Verner Reed and "DR" at United Nations (UN) event, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Joseph Verner Reed and George Bush at Alfalfa Dinner (Washington, D.C.), 1999 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - United Nations (UN) "Poster Opening" Ceremony -- Joseph Verner Reed and Kofi Anan, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Joseph Verner Reed, Myanmar, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Joseph Verner Reed and Ban-Ki Moon, 2007 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Joseph Verner Reed and George Bush, Undated (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Joseph Verner Reed, George Bush, and General Colin Powell, Undated (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Joseph Verner Reed portraits, Undated (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Joseph Verner Reed and President Richard M. Nixon in Morocco, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Joseph Verner Reed and President Ronald Reagan, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    Matte of photograph and accompanying document removed due to damage.
  - Joseph Verner Reed at Morocco event, Circa 1984 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - United Nations (UN) at 50, Circa 1995 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Joseph Verner Reed and Ronald Reagan, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    Matte of autographed photograph with companion letter of congratulations for service in Morocco.
  - Joseph Verner Reed and Unired Nations Representative Vernon A. Walters, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    Matte of photograph with companion letter from United States Mission to the United Nations.
  - Sketch of Joseph Verner Reed by Glen Edwards, Undated (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Joseph Verner Reed in Egypt, Undated (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Reed Family scrapbook fragments, Undated (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Additional Material, 2006-2014; Accession 2016-M-088
  This accession includes correspondence; memorabilia; a small framed print of the Mary Reed Library at the University of Denver; and photographs, including two portraits of Joseph Verner Reed, and a photograph album presented to Reed by the China International Publishing Group (CIPG).
  - Memorabilia, 2006-2013 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
  - Print of the Mary Reed Library at the University of Denver, Circa 2006-2013 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Photograph Album, Circa 2006-2013 (Box 3)
  - Photographs of Joseph Verner Reed, Circa 2006-2013 (Folder 4)